cipro.gov.za 2003-02-15

# CIPRO - Contact Us

The Companies & Intellectual Property Registration Office ("CIPRO") is committed to protecting the privacy of our customer's personal information. This Policy explains how we gather and use the information that we collect from our Web site, located at CIPRO.gov.za. This policy may change over time. Amendments to this statement will be posted at this URL and will be effective when posted. Your continued use of this site following the posting of any amendment, modification or change shall constitute your acceptance thereof. 

**Information Collected**

> As you navigate within our Web site, we will be collecting and tracking personal information, either by asking you to tell us something about yourself (such as your name, address or e-mail address) or by using data-tracking software which records your IP address and tells us what parts of the Web Site you have browsed. 

**Use of Information**

> This information is used to enhance your site experience, or to apply special benefits. Your personal information will not be sold to third parties for e-mail marketing or telemarketing campaigns. 
> 
> The information may be used by CIPRO or designated site partners to send you information that we think will be useful to you. 
> 
> Due to the technology behind the CIPRO site, your personal information may also be shared with designated site partners in order to reduce the number of registrations you need to make on the CIPRO site. This is an effort to make use of the CIPRO.gov.za site more convenient for you. 
> 
> You may opt-out of receiving future mailings from CIPRO and other entities by following the instructions set forth in the opt-out section below. 
> 
> Personal information about you, whether obtained through collection or tracking, may be used to contact you again either by online electronic communication (such as e-mail), or by regular mail or telephone. We will also be collecting and tracking information about activities in our Web site on an aggregate (i.e., group basis). We will not know or keep track of precisely who you are as you use the site. The data is used to track what areas of the site are most frequently used to help us improve the site in the future. When we share such information with other companies, it is not traceable to any particular user and will not be used to contact you again. 
> 
> Non-personal demographic and profile data is used to tailor your experience at our site, showing you content we think you might be interested in. This information may also be shared with advertisers on an aggregate non-personal basis. 
> 
> We may share your information (as described above) with our business partners to provide you with products or services that you have requested or to provide you with promotional offers that we believe will be of interest to you. Our business partners include all of our affiliated companies as well as other selected businesses with which we have a relationship and which have agreed to adhere to our strict standards for providing quality products and services, responding to your needs, and protecting customer information. We may also employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance (including direct and targeted marketing), processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. 
> 
> In certain circumstances, we may share your customer information with trusted service providers that need access to your information to provide operational or other support services. We also may provide information to regulatory authorities and law enforcement officials in accordance with applicable law or when we otherwise believe in good faith that the law requires it. In the event of a sale of all or part of one of our businesses, we may share customer information related to that business as part of the transaction. 

**Use of IP Address**

> We may use your IP Address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. 

**Use of Cookies**

> When you view our Web site we might store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "cookie" or similar file. Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your hard drive, not on our site. Cookies do not spy on you or otherwise invade your privacy, and they cannot invade your hard drive and steal information. Rather, they help you navigate a Web site as easily as possible. We use cookies for remembering user names, to identify users and their preferences, tracking click streams and for load balancing. Because of our use of cookies, we can deliver faster service, consistent, updated results and a more personalized site experience. You have the option of setting your browser to reject cookies. However, doing this will hinder performance and negatively impact your experience on our site. 

**Children**

> We do not specifically collect online contact information from children nor do we target or sell products for purchase by children. 

**Security**

> This Web site has industry standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. While there is no such thing as "perfect security" on the Internet, we will take reasonable steps to insure the safety of your personal information. 

**Other Web Sites' Links**

> This Web site contains links to other Web sites. CIPRO is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. If you want to know the privacy policies of the other Web sites, please refer to the organization sponsoring such Web site. 

**Consent**

> By visiting the CIPRO site, you expressly consent to the collection and use by CIPRO of personally identifiable information according to this Privacy Policy. 

**Choice; Opt Out**

> You may opt-out of receiving communications from CIPRO or our site partners by sending an e-mail to **[webz@cipro.gov.za](mailto:webz@cipro.gov.za)**.

**Correct; Update**

> CIPRO allows its users the ability to correct or update online information previously provided by the users. Unfortunately, to the extent that such information is also stored in other databases, we cannot always ensure that such corrections or deletions will reach the other databases. We will use all reasonable efforts to ensure that your information is removed from or corrected in our records. 

**Contact Us**

> If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us at **[webz@cipro.gov.za](mailto:webz@cipro.gov.za)**.
